{
  "Q": [
    {
      "question": "best synonym for chronicle",
      "answer1": "narrative",
      "answer2": "qualification",
      "answer3": "outline",
      "answer4": "entrance",
      "rightAnswer": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "best synonym for knock",
      "answer1": "know",
      "answer2": "belive",
      "answer3": "hit",
      "answer4": "shut",
      "rightAnswer": "3"
    },
    {
      "question": "best synonym for beg",
      "answer1": "stand",
      "answer2": "sit",
      "answer3": "hang",
      "answer4": "ask",
      "rightAnswer": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "best synonym for prior",
      "answer1": "senior",
      "answer2": "loyal",
      "answer3": "previous",
      "answer4": "retired",
      "rightAnswer": "3"
    },
    {
      "question": "best synonym for wrist",
      "answer1": "part of the arm",
      "answer2": "part of a car",
      "answer3": "part of a chair",
      "answer4": "part of a shoe",
      "rightAnswer": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "best synonym for ancient",
      "answer1": "anxious",
      "answer2": "old",
      "answer3": "financial",
      "answer4": "dangerous",
      "rightAnswer": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "best synonym for alleviate",
      "answer1": "go through",
      "answer2": "make worse",
      "answer3": "rush",
      "answer4": "relieve",
      "rightAnswer": "4"
    }
  ,
    {
      "question": "best synonym for evaluate",
      "answer1": "assess",
      "answer2": "award",
      "answer3": "impress",
      "answer4": "indicate",
      "rightAnswer": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "best synonym for soil",
      "answer1": "corn",
      "answer2": "leaf",
      "answer3": "bean",
      "answer4": "dirt",
      "rightAnswer": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "best synonym for dense",
      "answer1": "general",
      "answer2": "tail",
      "answer3": "tense",
      "answer4": "thick",
      "rightAnswer": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "best synonym for caring",
      "answer1": "healthy",
      "answer2": "confident",
      "answer3": "cool",
      "answer4": "kind",
      "rightAnswer": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "best synonym for nearby",
      "answer1": "close",
      "answer2": "almost",
      "answer3": "tiny",
      "answer4": "empty",
      "rightAnswer": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "best synonym for pond",
      "answer1": "face cream",
      "answer2": "generous person",
      "answer3": "small lake",
      "answer4": "makeup for the lips",
      "rightAnswer": "3"
    }
  ,
    {
      "question": "best synonym for confine",
      "answer1": "confide",
      "answer2": "regulate",
      "answer3": "restrict",
      "answer4": "detect",
      "rightAnswer": "3"
    },
    {
      "question": "best synonym for cool",
      "answer1": "excited",
      "answer2": "chill",
      "answer3": "temperate",
      "answer4": "friendly",
      "rightAnswer": "2"
    }
  ]
}